Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1972-1982. (Box 293, Folder 5)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries - (Reacquisition of permanent collection)., 1982. (Box 293, Folder 6)
- Index: X61/A7. Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1982-1984. (Box 294, Folder 1)
- Index: X61/A7. Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries - (UCLA Art Council)., 1976-1985. (Box 294, Folder 2)
- Index: X61/A7. Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1985-1986. (Box 294, Folder 3)
- Index: X61/A7. Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1986-1988. (Box 294, Folder 4)
- Index: X61/A7. Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries - (Wight Gallery Air Conditioning Project)., 1985-1988. (Box 294, Folder 5)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries - (Rifkind Collection)., 1976-1988. (Box 294, Folder 6)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1967-1974. (Box 295, Folder 1)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries - (Willits J. Hole Collection)., 1938-1974. (Box 295, Folder 2)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1973-1977. (Box 295, Folder 3)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1962-1978. (Box 295, Folder 4)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1977-1979. (Box 295, Folder 5)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1978-1981. (Box 295, Folder 6)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1978-1990. (Box 296, Folder 1)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1987-1990. (Box 296, Folder 2)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1985-1994. (Box 296, Folder 3)
- Index: X61/A7. Organized Research & Museums - Museums and Special Collections - General - Art Galleries., 1986-1996. (Box 296, Folder 4)
- Index: IB1 (A-D). Cooperation, Aid, & Information for Outside Entities - Business Organizations., 1971-1995. (Box 296, Folder 5)
- Index: IB1 (H-T). Cooperation, Aid, & Information for Outside Entities - Business Organizations., 1971-1996. (Box 296, Folder 6)
- Index: IB1 (U-X). Cooperation, Aid, & Information for Outside Entities - Business Organizations., 1974-1997. (Box 296, Folder 7)
- Index: EA93. Campus Management - Finance - Accounting - General., 1971-1976. (Box 297, Folder 1)
- Index: EA93. Campus Management - Finance - Accounting - General., 1977-1979. (Box 297, Folder 2)
- Index: EA93. Campus Management - Finance - Accounting - General., 1980-1983. (Box 297, Folder 3)
- Index: EA93. Campus Management - Finance - Accounting - General., 1972-1987. (Box 297, Folder 4)
- Index: EA93. Campus Management - Finance - Accounting - General., 1972-1995. (Box 297, Folder 5)
- Index: K19. Extramural Support - United States - General., 1971-1996. (Box 297, Folder 6)
- Index: A28-01. Board of Regents - Treasurer - General - Revenue Bonds., 1981-1986. (Box 298, Folder 1)
- Index: A28-01. Board of Regents - Treasurer - General - Revenue Bonds., 1986-1988. (Box 298, Folder 2)
- Index: A28-01. Board of Regents - Treasurer - General - Revenue Bonds., 1988-1989. (Box 298, Folder 3)
- Index: A28-01. Board of Regents - Treasurer - General - Revenue Bonds., 1989-1991. (Box 298, Folder 4)
- Index: A28-01. Board of Regents - Treasurer - General - Revenue Bonds., 1991-1993. (Box 299, Folder 1)
- Index: A28-01. Board of Regents - Treasurer - General - Revenue Bonds., 1979-1997. (Box 299, Folder 2)
- Index: A44. Board of Regents - Meetings - General., 1975-1984. (Box 299, Folder 3)
- Index: A44. Board of Regents - Meetings - General., 1985-1986. (Box 299, Folder 4)
- Index: A44. Board of Regents - Meetings - General., 1983-1986. (Box 299, Folder 5)
- Index: A47. Board of Regents - Meetings - Agendas., 1975-1988. (Box 299, Folder 6)
- Index: A47. Board of Regents - Meetings - Agendas., 1982-1993. (Box 300, Folder 1)
- Index: A47. Board of Regents - Meetings - Agendas., 1978-1997. (Box 300, Folder 2)
- Index: A76-01. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - General - Rosters (membership cards)., 1972-1997. (Box 300, Folder 3)
- Index: A76-02. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - General - Student Regent., 1974-1994. (Box 300, Folder 4)
- Index: A76-01. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - General - Membership., 1984-1996. (Box 300, Folder 5)
- Index: A76. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - General., 1974-1989. (Box 301, Folder 1)
- Index: A76. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - General., 1990-1992. (Box 301, Folder 2)
- Index: A76. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - General., 1993-1996. (Box 301, Folder 3)
- Index: A78-02. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - General - Student Regent., 1994-1996. (Box 301, Folder 4)
- Index: BB37. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Staff Personnel., 1981-1995. (Box 301, Folder 5)
- Index: BB37-01. Board of Regents -Membership of the Board - General - Chicano/Latino Consortium., 1989-1992. (Box 301, Folder 6)
- Index: BB37. Board of Regents -Membership of the Board - General - (UC Black Administrators)., 1989-1997. (Box 301, Folder 7)
- Index: BB37. Board of Regents -Membership of the Board - General., 1991-1997. (Box 301, Folder 8)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General., 1970-1979. (Box 302, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General - (Long Range Plng)., 1979. (Box 302, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Pyscial & Fiscal Planning - General - (Enrollment Trends., 1978-1980. (Box 302, Folder 3)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Pyscial & Fiscal Planning - General., 1979-1985. (Box 302, Folder 4)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General., 1986-1988. (Box 302, Folder 5)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Pyscial & Fiscal Planning - General - (Humanities Inst.)., 1986-1987. (Box 303, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General., 1986-1988. (Box 303, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4-04. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General - Teacher Prep Prog., 1988-1991. (Box 303, Folder 3)
- Index: BL4-02. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General - PACUE Conferences., 1988-1991. (Box 303, Folder 4)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General., 1988-1993. (Box 303, Folder 5)
- Index: BL4-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General - Humanities Inst., 1987-1992. (Box 304, Folder 1)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Pyscial & Fiscal Planning - General., 1993. (Box 304, Folder 2)
- Index: BL4-02. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General - PACUE Conf., 1992-1994. (Box 304, Folder 3)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Pyscial & Fiscal Planning - General., 1992-1994. (Box 304, Folder 4)
- Index: BL4. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning & Analysis - Coordination of Academic, Physical & Fiscal Planning - General., 1994-1995. (Box 304, Folder 5)
- Index: BT1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General., 1977-1978. (Box 304, Folder 6)
- Index: BT1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General., 1979. (Box 304, Folder 7)
- Index: BT1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General., 1979. (Box 305, Folder 1)
- Index: BT1-02. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General - Human Corps., 1986-1990. (Box 305, Folder 2)
- Index: BT1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General., 1990-1994. (Box 305, Folder 3)
- Index: BT1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General., 1994-1996. (Box 305, Folder 4)
- Index: BT1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General., 1993-1995. (Box 305, Folder 5)
- Index: BT1-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General - VC Stud Affairs Mtgs., 1990-1997. (Box 305, Folder 6)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1992. (Box 306, Folder 1)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1992. (Box 306, Folder 2)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1992. (Box 306, Folder 3)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1992-1993. (Box 306, Folder 4)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1992-1993. (Box 306, Folder 5)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1992-1993. (Box 306, Folder 6)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1993. (Box 307, Folder 1)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1993-1994. (Box 307, Folder 2)
- Index: JD1/R4. Governmental Relations - Los Angeles City - General - Rebuild Los Angeles., 1994-1996. (Box 307, Folder 3)
- Index: W28. Instructional Support Units -- Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems - Systems - (Centralized Mailing System)., 1978-1994. (Box 307, Folder 4)
- Index: W28. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems - Systems., 1975-1982. (Box 307, Folder 5)
- Index: W28. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems - Systems - (Athletic Dept and CTO Computer System)., 1981-1990. (Box 307, Folder 6)
- Index: W28. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems - Systems., 1983-1994. (Box 307, Folder 7)
- Index: VE2. Instructional Units - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences - Buildings, Space & Equipment., 1979-1985. (Box 308, Folder 1)
- Index: VE2. Instructional Units - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences - Buildings, Space & Equipment., 1983-1986. (Box 308, Folder 2)
- Index: VE2. Instructional Units - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences - Buildings, Space & Equipment., 1986-1987. (Box 308, Folder 3)
- Index: VE2. Instructional Units - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences - Buildings, Space & Equipment., 1986-1990. (Box 308, Folder 4)
- Index: VE2. Instructional Units - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences - Buildings, Space & Equipment., 1987-1991. (Box 308, Folder 5)
- Index: VE2. Instructional Units - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences - Buildings, Space & Equipment., 1991-1992. (Box 308, Folder 6)
- Index: A34. Board of Regents - Treasurer - Investment Officer & Analyst., 1976-1992. (Box 309, Folder 1)
- Index: A31. Board of Regents - Treasurer - Real Estate Officer., 1988-1994. (Box 309, Folder 2)
- Index: A85. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - Visits to Campus., 1970-1974. (Box 309, Folder 3)
- Index: A85. Board of Regents - Membership of the Board - Visits to Campus., 1974-1995. (Box 309, Folder 4)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1990-1996. (Box 309, Folder 5)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1995-1997. (Box 309, Folder 6)
- Index: BF13-01. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Financial Aid - Coordination - (Report on Student Aid - to Regents)., 1996. (Box 309, Folder 7)
- Index: BD1. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Business and Finance - General., 1970-1971. (Box 310, Folder 1)
- Index: BD1. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Business and Finance - General., 1977. (Box 310, Folder 2)
- Index: BD1. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Business and Finance - General., 1984-1989. (Box 310, Folder 3)
- Index: BD1. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Business and Finance - General., 1980-1991. (Box 310, Folder 4)
- Index: BD1. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Business and Finance - General., 1986-1992. (Box 310, Folder 5)
- Index: BD1. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Business and Finance - General., 1985-1994. (Box 310, Folder 6)
- Index: BD1. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Business and Finance - General., 1992-1994. (Box 310, Folder 7)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1981-1986. (Box 311, Folder 1)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1985-1986. (Box 311, Folder 2)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1985-1986. (Box 311, Folder 3)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1985-1987. (Box 311, Folder 4)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1985-1991. (Box 311, Folder 5)
- Index: BF4. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Admissions., 1988-1991. (Box 311, Folder 6)
- Index: BF13. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Financial Aid - Coordination., 1970-1976. (Box 312, Folder 1)
- Index: BF13. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Financial Aid - Coordination - (Student Loan Collection Decentralization)., 1977-1978. (Box 312, Folder 2)
- Index: BF13. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Financial Aid - Coordination., 1982-1986. (Box 312, Folder 3)
- Index: BF13. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Financial Aid - Coordination - (Report on Student Aid to the Regents)., 1989-1992. (Box 312, Folder 4)
- Index: BF13. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Financial Aid - Coordination., 1987-1995. (Box 312, Folder 5)
- Index: BF13. Systemwide Administration and Academic Senate - Educational Relations - Financial Aid - Coordination - (Report on Student Aid (to Regents)., 1993-1995. (Box 312, Folder 6)
- Index: C1. University of California Campuses - Berkeley., 1973-1986. (Box 313, Folder 1)
- Index: C1. University of California Campuses - Berkeley., 1989-1991. (Box 313, Folder 2)
- Index: C1. University of California Campuses - Berkeley., 1991. (Box 313, Folder 3)
- Index: C1. University of California Campuses - Berkeley., 1991-1993. (Box 313, Folder 4)
- Index: C1. University of California Campuses - Berkeley., 1993-1994. (Box 313, Folder 5)
- Index: C1. University of California Campuses - Berkeley., 1994-1997. (Box 313, Folder 6)
- Index: C11. University of California Campuses - Davis., 1974-1993. (Box 314, Folder 1)
- Index: C11. University of California Campuses - Davis., 1994-1996. (Box 314, Folder 2)
- Index: C31. University of California Campuses - Irvine., 1974-1997. (Box 314, Folder 3)
- Index: C41. University of California Campuses - Riverside., 1986-1997. (Box 314, Folder 4)
- Index: C51. University of California Campuses - San Diego., 1969-1994. (Box 314, Folder 5)
- Index: C51. University of California Campuses - San Diego., 1995-1997. (Box 314, Folder 6)
- Index: C61. University of California Campuses - San Francisco., 1973-1981. (Box 315, Folder 1)
- Index: C61. University of California Campuses - San Francisco., 1989. (Box 315, Folder 2)
- Index: C61. University of California Campuses - San Francisco., 1992-1996. (Box 315, Folder 3)
- Index: C81. University of California Campuses - Santa Barbara., 1978-1994. (Box 315, Folder 4)
- Index: C91. University of California Campuses - Santa Cruz., 1976-1996. (Box 315, Folder 5)
- Index: DA59. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Invitations, Thanks & Requests - Affairs., 1971-1997. (Box 315, Folder 6)
- Index: DA69/C3. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Challenger Center for Space Science Education., 1988-1990. (Box 315, Folder 7)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1988-1990. (Box 316, Folder 1)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1989-1990. (Box 316, Folder 2)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1990-1992. (Box 316, Folder 3)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1991-1993. (Box 316, Folder 4)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1992-1993. (Box 316, Folder 5)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1988-1994. (Box 316, Folder 6)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1996-1997. (Box 317, Folder 1)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1988-1996. (Box 317, Folder 2)
- Index: DA69/G6. Campus Admin & LA Div Acad Sen. - Chan's Ofc - Chan's Files - Mbrships - Outside Cmtes, Boards - Gov't University Industry Research Roundtable (GUIRR)., 1989-1994. (Box 317, Folder 3)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - - Administration & Staff., 1991-1992. (Box 317, Folder 4)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - Administration & Staff., 1989-1993. (Box 317, Folder 5)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - Administration & Staff., 1976-1978. (Box 318, Folder 1)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - Administration & Staff., 1977-1978. (Box 318, Folder 2)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - Administration & Staff., 1979-1982. (Box 318, Folder 3)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - Administration & Staff., 1983-1984. (Box 318, Folder 4)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - Administration & Staff., 1984-1989. (Box 318, Folder 5)
- Index: EM4. Campus Management - Campus Programming & Activities - Administration & Staff., 1983-1990. (Box 318, Folder 6)
- Index: K1. Extramural Support - General., 1987. (Box 319, Folder 1)
- Index: K1-04. Extramural Support - General (Software Services Center)., 1985-1989. (Box 319, Folder 2)
- Index: K1-03. Extramural Support - General (OCGA Award Comparison Report)., 1987-1992. (Box 319, Folder 3)
- Index: K1. Extramural Support - General., 1975-1994. (Folder 4)
- Index: K1. Extramural Support - General., 1975-1994. (Box 319, Folder 5)
- Index: K1. Extramural Support - General., 1987-1996. (Box 320, Folder 1)
- Index: K1. Extramural Support - General., 1993-1997. (Box 320, Folder 2)
- Index: K19/N4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation., 1971-1980. (Box 320, Folder 3)
- Index: K19/N4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation., 1981-1985. (Box 320, Folder 4)
- Index: K19/N4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation., 1986-1987. (Box 320, Folder 5)
- Index: K19/N4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation., 1986-1987. (Box 320, Folder 6)
- Index: K19/N4-01. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation - (Presidential Young Investigator Award)., 1983-1987. (Box 321, Folder 1)
- Index: K19/N4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation., 1977. (Box 321, Folder 2)
- Index: K19/N4-02. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation - Florida Demonstration Project., 1987-1988. (Box 321, Folder 3)
- Index: K19/N4-03. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation - NSF ERC Integrated Signal Processing., 1986-1989. (Box 321, Folder 4)
- Index: K19/N4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (Includes Federal Demon. Proj)., 1987-1989. (Box 321, Folder 5)
- Index: K19/N4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (Includes Federal Demon. Proj; Call for Proposals NSF Sci & Tech Ctrs)., 1989-1990. (Box 321, Folder 6)
- Index: K19/N4-05. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (Federal Demonstration Project)., 1990. (Box 322, Folder 1)
- Index: K19/N4-06. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (NSF Salary Limitation)., 1989-1991. (Box 322, Folder 2)
- Index: K19/N4-05. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (Federal Demonstration Project)., 1990-1991. (Box 322, Folder 3)
- Index: K19/N4-01. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (Presidential Young Investigator Award)., 1987-1992. (Box 322, Folder 4)
- Index: K19/N4-01 & -05. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (PYI Award and Federal Demonstration Project)., 1990-1993. (Box 322, Folder 5)
- Index: K19/N4-09, 7,5. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation (Important Notices; Visiting Professorships for Women; Federal Demonstration)., 1987-1997. (Box 322, Folder 6)
- Index: K19/N4A6. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation - Appropriations., 1976-1979. (Box 323, Folder 1)
- Index: K19/N4R4. Extramural Support - United States - National Science Foundation - Research Applied to National Needs (RANN)., 1972-1975. (Box 323, Folder 2)